Marist Student Government Association Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 14. 1998
  - Subseries 14.2: Legislation
    - The McCulloch Bill for Bookstore Price Awareness, November 30, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Bill for Increased Parking (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Subseries 14.3: Clubs
    - Commuter Student Council By-laws, April 20, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Delta Iota Colony By-laws, March 1, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Habitat for Humanity By-laws, April 27, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Habitat for Humanity Covenant, April 27, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - SGA By-laws and Constitution (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Subseries 14.4: Events
    - ACUI Conference, Fall 1998 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - ACUI Conference Campus Maps (CIA, Dutchess, Vassar, Bard), Fall 1998 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - SGA Summit, January 31, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - SGA Day, February 4, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Subseries 14.5: Allocations
    - Circle Advertisement Bill (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Fall '98 Allocations, April 1, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Fall '98 Semeser Additional Allocations, October 7, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Financial Board Allocations Examples, May 24, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Instructions for Budget Requests, March 1, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Spring '98 Additional Allocations (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Spring '99 Allocations, November 12, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 14.6: Reports
    Extent: 10 folders
    - Safety and Security Report, April 6, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Spring '98 Elections, Spring 1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Spring '98 Club Review, Spring 1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Club Review, July 19, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Club Officers Focus Group Report, September 22, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Event Evaluation Form, November 1, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Crisis Management Prevention (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Executive & Senatorial Reports (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Interim Year Changes (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Vision 2000: Library (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 14.7: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Memoranda (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 14.8: Misc.
    - SGA Code of Ethics (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - SGA "Get Involved!" Flyer Copy Request Form (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - SGA Press (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - SGA Press Conference, September 20, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - SGA Management by Objective (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Notes (Box 9, Folder 22)
- 15. 1999
  - Subseries 15.1: Meetings
    - Class Council Meeting, 1905-06-21 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - SGA Summer Sessions, July 15-18, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - SLC Meetings (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 15.2: Legislation
    Extent: 29 folders
    - Effective Organizations Committee Mission Statements, January 27, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 1999 Transition Plans, February 3, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Bill to Amend Financial Board Guidelines, February 8, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 1999 Spring Reallocations, February 23, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The J.D.S. Bill for Speech Night Seating Arrangements, March 2, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - The McCulloch Bill for Increased Public Awareness, March 4, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, March 5, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Bill for Faculty of the Year Elections, March 31, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Legislation, April 6, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Legislation, April 19, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 1999 Fall Budget Bill, April 23, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Legislation, April 26, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Bill to Establish the Position of an Assistant Chief Finance Officer, April 27, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Commuter Lounge Relocation Committee, April 28, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Legislation, May 3, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Legislation, July 13, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, July 17, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Bill for Continuing to Voice Student Concerns, September 1, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - SLC-Campus Investigation Plans and Coordination with Local Police, September 7, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Marist College School Spirit Committee, September 13, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Mission Statement for Housing and Residential Life Committee, September 24, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 1999 Fall Reallocations, September 27, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Project Unity Committee, October 19, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Bill for Creation of a New Club Council, November 15, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The 2000 Transition Plan, November 30, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - The Residence Hall Association Bill, December 2, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Feb 2000 Elections Calendar, December 6, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Bill for Elections Packet Clarifications, December 7, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - SGA Bills: Hunter Administration (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Subseries 15.3: Clubs
    - Asian Alliance By-laws, November 8, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Revised By-laws: Marist College Band, September 20, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Fencing Club By-laws, October 18, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - MCCTA By-laws, September 17, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Poughkeepsie Institute '99 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - SGA Constitution (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Subseries 15.4: Events
    - Fall Elections Calendar, September 1, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Open House Sign-up Sheets (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Recognition Awards, February 4, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - SGA Day 1999, February 2, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Subseries 15.5: Allocations
    - Fall '99 Allocations, April 22, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - SGA Member Payments (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Subseries 15.6: Reports
    - President's Report Drafts, February 10, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Diversity Day Progress Report, March 5, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Club Review: 1998-1999, July 17, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Library Report (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - SGA Goals 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Subseries 15.7: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Memorandum (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Subseries 15.8: Misc.
    - CIA Informational Magazine (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Commuter Senator Candidates, February 17, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Kristine A Dunn Letter of Resignation, November 3, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Notes (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Sample Elections Letter, July 14, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - SGA Press (Box 10, Folder 55)
- 16. 2000
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, events, reports, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 16.1: Meetings
    Extent: 15 folders
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, March 2, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Executive Session, November 28, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - List for Joint Meetings (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - RSC Meetings (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Student Life Council Meetings (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Summer Session Schedule (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Unity Day Meetings (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 16.2: Legislation
    - Bill to Establish the Adrian Award for Excellence in Club Leadership, February 7, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Referendum Question for Spring 2000 Election, February 16, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Spring 2000 Reallocations, February 18, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Bill to Formally Recognize Marcellin Champagnat's Canonization, February 28, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Constitutional Amendment Article III Section 3 Letter G, February 29, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Mission Statement for the Housing and Residential Life Committee, April 10, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 2000 Calendars, April 18, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Legislation, April 25, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 2000 Budget Bill, April 30, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Mission Statement for the SGA "Student Speaks" Committee, May 2, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Legislation, July 26, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Legislation, September 11, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Bill to Establish the Marist College Student Traffic Appeals Court, September 19, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Bill to Amend the Marist College Student Government Association By-laws Appendix E, October 1, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Legislation, October 2, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Legislation, October 11, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Bill to Amend the SGA Constitutional By-laws, October 30, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Spring 2001 Budget Bill, November 27, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Bill to Amend the Financial Board Guidelines, December 11, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Information Technology Proposal (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills List - Tyminski Administration (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Executive Bills List (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 16.3: Clubs
    Extent: 17 folders
    - Advertising Club By-laws, April 10, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Department of Athletics: Compliance Policies + Procedures Manual [1 of 2], Summer 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Department of Athletics: Compliance Policies + Procedures Manual [2 of 2], Summer 2000 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Department of Athletics Camps/Clinics Manual, Summer 2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Marist College Band By-laws, March 20, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Bowling Club By-laws, September 24, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Fencing Club By-laws, February 22, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - History Club By-laws, February 8, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Kappa Kappa Psi/Tau Beta Sigma By-laws, March 9, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Lambda Pi Eta Honor Society By-laws, April 25, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Public Relations Committee By-laws (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Resident hall Association By-laws (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Sigma Gamma Rho By-laws, May 2, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - SGA Code of Ethics (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Student Programming CFO Manual (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Student Programming Council By-laws, September 1, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Zeta Psi By-laws, May 2, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Subseries 16.4: Events
    - SGA Transition Awards, November 10, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Spring Elections 2001, November 27, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Fall Elections (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Subseries 16.5: Reports
    - Unity Day Report, February 27, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Unity Day Report, March 5, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - The Class of 2001, April 19, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Dennis Murray Board Meeting Update, April 28, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Campus Parking and Vehicle Usage Policy, August 1, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Dennis Murray: Update on College Activities, September 8, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Marist Student Traffic Court Interim Report, October 1, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Dennis Murray Board Meeting Update, October 27, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Safety and Security Committee Report, November 14, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - The Jones Report (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Subseries 16.6: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Memoranda (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Subseries 16.8: Misc.
    - "The Soul of a New University", March 13, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Elections Guidelines (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - SGA Press (Box 11, Folder 42)
- 17. 2001
  - Subseries 17.1: Meetings
    Extent: 11 folders
    - Board of Trustees Meeting (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Executive Board Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Joint Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - RSC Meetings (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Senate Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - SGA Summer Session, July 19-22, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Student Life Council Meetings (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - SLC Meetings [Duplicates] (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 17.2: Legislation
    Extent: 22 folders
    - Safety and Security Mission Statement 2, January 29, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Bill to Establish the Marist College Professional Code of Ethics, January 30, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Legislation, February 9, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Legislation, February 22, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 2001 Transition Plan, February 26, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Bill to Amend SGA Advisory Council Operational Guidelines and Procedures, March 19, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Legislation, April 2, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Bill to Amend SGA Elections Guidelines, April 6, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Bill to Amend Constitution for SGA, April 18, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Legislation, April 21, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Legislation, April 30, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Legislation, July 18, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Fall 2001 Elections Calendar, September 21, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Fall 2001 Budget Bill, July 22, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Legislation, September 2, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Mission Statement for the SGA "Alumni Affairs" Committee, September 18, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Legislation, September 25, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Mission Statement for the SGA "Student Speaks" Committee, October 1, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - The Fall 2001 Reallocation Budget Bill, November 7, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Bill to Approve Escort Policy for Safety and Security Committee, November 13, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - KCH/BCM Community Service Bill, December 7, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - The Spring 2002 Budget Bill, December 11, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Subseries 17.3: Clubs
    Extent: 8 folders
    - Adrian Award for Club Leadership, February 20, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Petitioning Chapter (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - International Students Club By-laws, February 22, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - RSC Handbook (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Resident Student Council By-laws (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - RSC Leadership Conference, October 29, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - RSC Members (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - SLC/RSC Papers (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Subseries 17.4: Events
    - "A Night Among the Heavens" Event, April 20, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Rally and March for Peace Flyer, October 27, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - SGA Family and Friends Day, December 8, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - February 2002 Elections Calendar, December 11, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Unity Day (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Subseries 17.5: Allocations
    - Class of '02 Allocation Request, Fall 2001 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Subseries 17.6: Reports
    - Marist Athletics Self-study (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Executive Conference Evaluation (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Hogan Administration Outlook Portfolio (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Middle States Accreditation (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Middle States Review: IT (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Programming Committees (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Subseries 17.7: Correspondence
    - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Memoranda/Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Dennis Murray Board Meeting Update, January 26, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@1)
    - Transition Letter, March 30, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@2)
  - Subseries 17.8: Misc.
    Extent: 14 folders
    - Proposed Library Hours for 2001-02, August 7, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@3)
    - Brian McAlpin Apology + Leave, September 19, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@4)
    - "Greening" for our College Libraries, September 25, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@5)
    - Student Exec: Hazing, September/October 2001 (Box 14, Folder@6)
    - Room Reservation, October 11, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@7)
    - SGA Town Hall Posters Copy Center Receipts, October 15, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@8)
    - Aaron Franchette "A New Vision for Marist", October 27, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@9)
    - Radio City Christmas Spectacular Flyer, November 17, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@10)
    - Student Speak Forms, December 1, 2001 (Box 14, Folder@11)
    - "Marist College Academics News", Fall 2001 (Box 14, Folder@12)
    - PlayRights Acquaintance Rape Templates (Box 14, Folder@13)
    - R.A.D. Pamphlet + Order Sheets (Box 14, Folder@14)
    - SGA Press (Box 14, Folder@15)
    - Traffic Court Interim Report (Box 14, Folder@16)
- 18. 2002
  - Subseries 18.1: Meetings
  - Subseries 18.2: Legislation
    - Academic Incentive Committee Mission Statement, February 1, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@19)
    - Legislation, February 26, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@20)
    - Adjunct Faculty of the Year Award Bill, April 2, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@21)
    - Minority Plan Proposal (Box 14, Folder@22)
  - Subseries 18.3: Clubs
    - Accounting Club By-laws, February 11, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@23)
    - Animal Rights Ninjas By-laws, November 2, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@24)
    - Anime Society By-laws, February 11, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@25)
    - Fashion Inc By-laws, March 4, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@26)
    - Gay Straight Alliance Proposals, March 4, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@27)
  - Subseries 18.4: Events
    - Class of 02 Publicity/Events (Box 14, Folder@28)
    - 9/11 Commemoration (Box 14, Folder@29)
    - Sexual Assault Awareness Campaign (Box 14, Folder@30)
  - Subseries 18.5: Allocations
    - Class of '02 Allocation Request, Spring 2002 (Box 14, Folder@31)
    - Class of '02 Event Expenses (Box 14, Folder@32)
    - Sodexho Catering Invoice (College Activities), February 14, 2002 (Box 14, Folder@33)
  - Subseries 18.6: Reports
    - Customer Satisfaction Survey Results, Fall 2002 (Box 14, Folder@34)
  - Subseries 18.7: Correspondence
    - Memoranda/Correspondence (Box 14, Folder@35)
  - Subseries 18.8: Misc.
    - Student Speaks Night Papers (Box 14, Folder@36)
- 19. 2003
  Series includes materials pertaining to SGA activities related to meetings, legislation, clubs, events, correspondence, and misc.
  - Subseries 19.1: Meetings
    - Board of Trustees Meetings, Fall 2003 (Box 14, Folder@37)
    - Dining Committee Meeting, February 11, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@38)
    - Executive Board Meetings (Box 14, Folder@39)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 14, Folder@40)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 14, Folder@41)
  - Subseries 19.2: Legislation
    - By-laws Amendments, September 9, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@42)
    - Legislation, September 24, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@43)
    - WMCR Fall 2003 Budgets for Clubs and Organizations, October 1, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@44)
    - Safety and Security Committee, October 15, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@45)
    - Legislation, October 29, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@46)
    - Acceptance of By-laws for IT Council, November 5, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@47)
    - Amendment to Class and Club Disciplinary Matrix, November 19, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@48)
    - 2003 Transition Plan (Box 14, Folder@49)
  - Subseries 19.3: Clubs
    - Fraternity Billing (Box 14, Folder@50)
    - Phi Kappa Sigma Letter, April 9, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@51)
    - Official Club Requirements for Club Websites, November 1, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@52)
  - Subseries 19.4: Events
    - Take Back the Hudson Valley, April 25, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@53)
    - Fall Elections '03, Fall 2003 (Box 14, Folder@54)
    - Individual Recognitions Awards (Box 14, Folder@55)
    - Speaker Hackett (Box 14, Folder@56)
  - Subseries 19.5: Correspondence
    - Complaint Emails (Box 14, Folder@57)
    - Fraternity Correspondence (Box 14, Folder@58)
  - Subseries 19.6: Misc.
    - Meeting with Brian Notes, March 4, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@59)
    - Student Center Room Reservation Form, March 26, 2003 (Box 14, Folder@60)
- 20. 2004
  - Subseries 20.1: Meetings
    - Committee B Meetings (Box 14, Folder@61)
    - Executive Meetings (Box 14, Folder@62)
    - Joint Meetings (Box 14, Folder@63)
    - Senate Meetings (Box 14, Folder@64)
    - Student Academic Council Meetings (Box 14, Folder@65)
  - Subseries 20.2: Legislation
    - Juras Resolution on Hazing, January 8, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Election Policies Bill, February 11, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Bill to Reinstate Club Advisor of the Year Award, February 25, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Legislation, March 31, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bill to Create an All Night Finals Week Coffee Bar, May 5, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Creation of the General Member Committee, September 15, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Senate Committee on Club Financial Relief, September 29, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Resident Senator Amendment Bill, October 6, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Creation of a Bylaws and Revisions Committee, October 27, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Creation of a Bylaws and Revisions Committee (2), November 10, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 20.3: Clubs
    - Circle K - President's Council Letter, September 11, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Circle K - How to Run a Meeting (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Marist Hockey Team By-laws (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 20.4: Allocations
    Extent: 41 folders
    - Alpha Phi Delta Allocations (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Alpha Sigma Tau Allocations (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - American Chemical Society Allocations (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Accounting Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Band Allocations (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Beta Alpha Psi Allocations (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Business Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Cheerleading Allocations (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Chess Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - The Circle Allocations (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Circle K Allocations (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Class of 2005 Allocations (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Class of 2007 Allocations (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Class of 2008 Allocations (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Communication Arts Society Allocations (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Commuter Student Council Allocations (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Computer Society Allocations (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Criminal Justice Society Allocations (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Dance Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Economics Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Fashion Inc. Allocations (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Gaelic Society Allocations (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Gender Equality Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Generator Allocations (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma Allocations (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Lambda Pi Eta Allocations (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Literary Arts Society Allocations (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Math Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - MCCTA Allocations (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - MCTV Allocations (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Model U.N. Allocations (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Phi Delta Epsilon Allocations (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Phi Kappa Sigma Allocations (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Pi Sigma Alpha Allocations (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - S.E.E.D. Allocations (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Sigma Sigma Sigma Allocations (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Social Work Association Allocations (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Teachers of Tomorrow Allocations (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Volleyball Club Allocations (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - WMAR Allocations (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Women's Rugby Allocations (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Zeta Psi Allocations (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Subseries 20.5: Reports
    - Appeals Procedures (Box 15, Folder 56)